wizer.me 2016-05-21

# wizer.me

Wizerme Privacy and Cookie Policy 

Last Revised: April 20, 2015 

Welcome to the Wizer.me Platform  a unique, user-friendly education platform for teachers ("  Wizer.me Platform  " or   “Platform”  )   brought to you  (“  you  ”,  “user”, or “teacher  ”)  by Wizerme L.S (2015) Ltd.  (“  Wizerme  ”, “we”, “us”, “our”  or the "  Company  "). 

We   respect the privacy of our users and are committed to protect the personal information that users share with us in connection with the use of  the Wizer.me Platform  . 

This Privacy and Cookie Policy (the "  Privacy Policy  ") is intended to describe our practices regarding the information we may collect from you when you use  the Wizer.me Platform  , the manners in which we may use such information, and the options and rights available to you. 

Capitalized terms which are not defined herein, shall have the meaning ascribed to them in our Terms and Conditions available at  www.wizer.me/terms    (the "  Terms  "), which this Privacy Policy is incorporated thereto by reference. 

Your Consent 

BY ACCESSING AND/OR USING THE WIZER.ME PLATFORM, YOU AGREE TO THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS SET FORTH IN THIS PRIVACY POLICY, INCLUDING TO THE COLLECTION AND PROCESSING OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION (AS DEFINED BELOW). IF YOU DISAGREE TO ANY TERM PROVIDED HEREIN, PLEASE DO NOT INSTALL, ACCESS, OR USE THE WIZER.ME PLATFORM IN ANY MANNER WHATSOEVER, AND PROMPTLY ERASE AND REMOVE THE WIZER.ME PLATFORM AND ANY PART THEREOF FROM YOUR SYSTEMS. 

Personal Identifiable Information from Children

In accordance with COPPA we do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information online from children who are under the age of 13. You represent and warrant that you are a teacher or school administrator or otherwise authorized by a school or district to sign up on behalf of students for the Service. You further represent and warrant that you are solely responsible for complying with COPPA, meaning that you may either act as the parent’s agent and consent to the collection of the children’s information on the parent’s behalf or obtain advance written consent from all parents or guardians whose children under 13 will be accessing the Service. When obtaining consent, you must provide parents and guardians with the Terms and this Privacy Policy. You must keep all consents on file and provide them to us if we request them. If you are a teacher, you represent and warrant that you have permission and authorization from your school and/or district to use the Services as part of your curriculum, and for purposes of COPPA compliance, you represent and warrant that you are entering into these Terms on behalf of your school and/or district. If you are a parent, guardian, and teacher and believe that your child or student has provided Wizerme with Personal Identifiable Information, you should notify us at  [support@wizer.me](mailto:support@wizer.me) so that we may immediately delete the information from our servers. 

Please note: you are not obligated by law to provide us with any Personal Information. You hereby acknowledge and agree that you are providing us with Personal Information at your own free will, for the purposes described below, and that we may retain such Personal Information in accordance with this Privacy Policy and any applicable laws and regulations. 

Information Collected from Users 

We may collect two types of data and information from our Users: 

  1. The first type of information is un-identified and non-identifiable information pertaining to a User(s), which may be made available or gathered via the User's use of  the Wizer.me Platform   (  “  Non-personal Information  ”  ).  We are not aware of the identity of the User from which the Non-personal Information was collected  . Non-personal Information which is being collected consists of technical information and aggregated usage information, and may contain, among other things, the activity of the User on  the Wizer.me Platform  , type of operation system, User's 'click-stream' on  the Wizer.me Platform   and/or any e-commerce websites operated by third parties (including Third Party Services, as such term is defined in the Terms), browser type, language and keyboard language, etc. 

  2. The second type of information is individually identifiable information, namely information that identifies an individual or may with reasonable effort identify an individual, or may be of private or sensitive nature (“  Personal Information  ”).   

Personal Information which may be gathered consists of the following: 

  * The User's IP address or other persistent user identifier, which is automatically provided by the User  and used mainly for enhancing the User's experience and for geolocation personalization and security purposes, as further detailed below; 
  * Any Personal Information provided voluntarily by the User via the Wizer.me Platform, such as the User's e-mail address in order to be contacted, the User's answers to questions presented to the User through the Wizer.me Platform, including the User’s full name and password, and/or other actions performed by the User in connection with the Wizer.me Platform; 
  * Any Personal Information provided voluntarily by the User via their Third Party Service accounts; 
  * Personal Information regarding Student Activity including timestamps and events for when a student accomplishes a particular assignment as designated by a User; and/or 
  * Personal information regarding User’s transactions on the Marketplace. 

For avoidance of doubt, any Non-personal Information connected or linked to any Personal Information shall be deemed as Personal Information as long as such connection or linkage exists. 

We do not collect any Personal Information from you or related to you without your approval, which is obtained,  inter alia  , through your active acceptance to the Terms and this Privacy Policy. 

How We Collect Information on Our Users 

There are two main methods we use: 

  1. We collect information through your use of the Wizer.me Platform  . In other words, when you are using the Wizer.me Platform we are aware of it and may gather, collect and record the information relating to such usage, either independently or through the help of third-party services as detailed below. 
  2. We collect information   which you provide us voluntarily  . For example,  we collect Personal Informatio  n which you voluntarily provide when you contact us directly. We may also collect Personal Information you voluntarily provide through integration with your Twitter, Facebook, Pinterest, Gmail and/or Edmodo account. 

We store the Personal Information either independently or through the help of our authorized third-party service providers as detailed below. 

Purposes of the Collection of Information 

We collect Non-personal and Personal Information in order to provide and operate  the Wizer.me Platform  , including for statistical and research purposes; to enable us to further develop, customize and improve  the Wizer.me Platform   based on Users common preferences and uses; and to enable us to provide our Users with a better user experience, with more relevant features and other materials, and with technical assistance and support. 

Sharing Information with Third Parties 

Wizerme will not share any Personal Information it collects with any third party. Notwithstanding the foregoing, we may disclose Personal Information in the following cases: (a) to satisfy any applicable law, regulation, legal process, subpoena or governmental request; (b) to enforce this Privacy Policy and/or the Terms, including investigation of potential violations thereof; (c) to detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues; (d) to respond to User's support requests; (e) to respond to claims that any content available on the Site violates the rights of third-parties; (f) to respond to claims that contact information (e.g. name, e-mail address, etc.) of a third-party has been posted or transmitted without their consent or as a form of harassment; (g) to protect the rights, property, or personal safety of Wizerme, its Users, or the general public; (h) when Wizerme or any of its affiliates is undergoing any change in control, including by means of merger, acquisition or purchase of all or substantially all of its assets; (i) to collect, hold and/or manage your Personal Information through the Wizerme 's authorized third party service providers, as reasonable for business purposes, which may be located in a country that does not have the same data protection laws as your jurisdiction; (j) pursuant to your explicit approval prior to the disclosure; or (k) to cooperate with third parties for the purpose of enhancing the User's experience. 

For avoidance of doubt, Wizerme may transfer and disclose to third parties or otherwise use  Non-personal Information   at its sole discretion. 

Deletion of Personal Information 

If for any reason you wish us to delete your Personal Information stored with us and identifying to you, please send us an e-mail to:    [support@wizer.me ](mailto:support@wizer.me)   and we will make reasonable efforts to delete any such Personal Information pursuant to any applicable privacy laws.    Note that unless you instruct us otherwise we may retain your Personal Information for a period of 7 years or a longer period as reasonably and legally required.   A parent of any student may contact us to delete the Personal Information of their child  and we will make reasonable efforts to delete any such Personal Information pursuant to any applicable privacy laws 

Security 

We take a great care in  implementing   and maintaining the security of  the Wizer.me Platform  , and  the User's Personal Information. The Personal Information is hosted on Heroku, which provides advanced security features. The Company employs industry standard procedures and policies to ensure the safety of its Users’ Personal Information, and prevent unauthorized use of any such information.  However, we do not and cannot guarantee that unauthorized access will never occur. 

Third Party Software/Service 

While using  the Wizer.me Platform   we may be using third party software and/or service, in order to collect and/or process the information detailed herein. Such software includes without limitation, Google Analytics, which privacy policy is available at  [http://www.google.com/intl/en/analytics/privacyoverview.html ](http://www.google.com/intl/en/analytics/privacyoverview.html) [[a] ](https://app.wizer.me/#cmnt1) ; and Heroku, which privacy policy is available at  [https://www.heroku.com/policy/privacy ](https://www.google.com/url?q=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.heroku.com%2Fpolicy%2Fprivacy&sa=D&sntz=1&usg=AFQjCNEY7ApjlInihpG2bcYEikT_JavTJw) . 

Third Party Services 

While using  the Wizer.me Platform   you may encounter links to Third Party Content and/or Third Party Services. Please be advised that such Third Party Services are independent from the Company, and if you click on any of these third party links, these Third Party Services may use cookies and other web-tracking technologies to collect non-personal and/or personal information about you.  We assume no responsibility or liability whatsoever with regard to privacy matters or any other legal matter with respect to such services. We encourage you to carefully read the privacy policies and the terms of use or service of such third parties, as their terms, not ours, will apply to any of your interactions with such third parties. 

Cookies 

When you access or use  the Wizer.me Platform  , Wizerme may use industry-wide technologies such as "cookies" (or similar technologies), which store certain information on your computer ("  Local Storage  ") and which will allow us to enable automatic activation of certain features, and make your service experience much more convenient and effortless. The cookies used by  the Wizer.me Platform   are created per session, do not include any information about you other than your session key, and are removed as your session ends. It is easy to prohibit the Local Storage. Most browsers will allow you to erase cookies from your computer's hard drive, block acceptance of cookies, or receive a warning before a cookie is stored. However, if you block or erase cookies your online experience may be limited. 

Changes to the Privacy Policy 

Wizerme reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time and at its sole discretion, so please re-visit this page frequently. We will provide notice of substantial changes of this Privacy Policy on the homepage of the Site and/or we will notify you via  the Wizer.me Platform   regarding such changes. Such substantial changes will take effect seven (7) days after such notice was provided on any of the abovementioned methods. Otherwise, all other changes to this Privacy Policy are effective as of the stated “Last Revised” date and your continued use of  the Wizer.me Platform   after the Last Revised date will constitute acceptance of, and agreement to be bound by, those changes. 

How to Contact Us 

If you have any questions (or comments) concerning this Privacy Policy, you are welcome to send us an e-mail at  :  [support@wizer.me ](mailto:support@wizer.me)   and we will make an effort to    reply within a reasonable timeframe.
